Hello, my name is Green and welcome back
to another episode of Hermitcraft. This
is excellent. Do you know why it's
excellent? Because we just got paid
Stash for Cash payment. That means that
someone has gone to the Stash for Cash
shop and decided that they too would
like to remove Mumbo's mustache. So,
Jevan has given me I think Jeban got the
price wrong. I think Jeban got very much
the price.
How? Wait, how many is this? 64 * 64.
Wait, how many diamonds has he given me?
Does that mean that's just my money now?
I did. He got the price wrong, but does
this He is very rich. Like, he's willing
to pay me three stacks of diamonds
and I have 20 27. I We are poor. So
maybe
maybe we just keep the money. Hold on. I
have a good idea.
This is really sneaky. We're going to go
back to the stash for cash shop. We're
going to go to the book. We're going to
check three stacks of diamond. I think
what it said was diamond blocks.
Oh. Oh, this is this is devious. This is
absolutely devious. So, what we're going
to do here is we're not actually going
to steal Jeban's diamonds. We're not a
thief on this server. Okay, we are
definitely not a thief, but we are going
to play this out for as long as
possible. Okay, we're going to make
Jevan think that it was actually three
stacks of diamond blocks. We will return
this money to Jebin at some point, but
not before me and Mumbo come up with a
good way to use it and spend it. Okay,
so bear in mind we're not stealing this.
But we are going to trick Jebin since he
decided not to read the book properly.
Unless you guys think I should just take
this money, in which case, let me know
in the comments. So, what we're going to
do is we're going to take this. I I
really want to know how many diamonds
this is. Oh my goodness.
Oh my good. There's so many. I can't
even fit them all in. So, that's a full
chest full of diamonds. That's more
money than me or Mumbo ever need. So,
okay. So, well, if he's willing to pay,
I'm um I'm willing to keep it. I don't
think I've ever seen this many diamond
this many diamonds on the floor. Okay.
So, I've turned this all back into
diamonds now. So, this is going to I'm
going to put this off to the side now.
Half is for me and half is for Mumbo
since we are going halvesies on this.
This is an architect project. So we are
going to have half each. Now that is
more money. Even half of that is more
money than I've got. So that is great.
Now Jevan is actually online at the
moment. So why don't we just message
him?
Also you might notice that in the base
I've actually put a trim around
everything. So before they were just
plain white pillars. So, what I've done
is I've taken some cyan terra cotta and
I've worked it all the way around and
around the pillars and also I made it uh
mimic the the ring around the middle as
well. And I think that's added quite a
lot. It's made it feel a bit more full
in here. I also tidied up some of these
walls a bit because they were looking a
bit um uneven in general, but there's
still something wrong with all of these.
Ah, Jevvin, he's just said, of course.
So, what we're going to do is we're
going to play this off as uh that he's
paid the full amount uh that is
described in the book. And if he goes
back to check, then he will definitely
see that it said diamond blocks. And he
won't know the difference. And we're
just going to see how long we can keep
this going. Oh, I was about to say I
just said come on over, bro. He's
already here. Hello, bro.
Hello. What's up, man?
Oh, not much. Not much. So, you are
actually the first ever customer for
Stash for Cash, which is mad. And you've
already given me payment. I've put that
away in my vault. Thank you very much.
For the low, low price of three stacks
of diamond blocks, I think it's totally
worth it, to be honest with you.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. That's Yeah, it's
definitely worth that much money. I'm
100% 100%. Um, so
shall I take you up? I mean, let's head
over. We got to fly up there.
Oh, you don't have to. I got a little
elevator as well.
Oh, look at you go.
It's better for the reveal of the
machine, you know.
[Applause]
That's awesome.
So, this is
I've never seen this before. So, this is
this is new for me.
This is my secret lab. And then like
behind me, you'll see like the architect
logo there. So, like this is a joint
venture.
I mean, Mumbo had to give me permission.
I'm just going to get rid of this beacon
here so we can get the full effect.
There we go. So beautiful. This is the
unnamed machine. I still haven't had a
good name for it yet. I mean, well, I've
seen loads of brilliant suggestions, but
none of them quite have uh hit the mark
yet. Some people are saying like just
the mustache remover type thing or like
giving it abbreviations. So, it's the um
unnamed machine, but the shop is Stash
for Cash.
I'm going to throw out a name here. It
doesn't have to stick.
Go on.
But I'm going to go with the the
Stashinator 9000. Stashing a 9,01.
Maybe.
There you go. Perfect. I mean, it's got
to be over 9,000. So,
I might I might actually do that. Let's
Let's uh put that in.
This is exciting. Now I don't have to
look at Mumbo's stash all day long.
I know, right? I mean, the whole reason
we created this is so we don't have to
look at his facial hair all the time.
Yeah.
But Have you seen Have you seen his face
without the mustache? It's actually a
little bit disturbing.
Oh god,
it looks all wrong. What are we actually
doing to ourselves if we think about
this? Maybe the stash is better. No,
no, no, no.
Like, no. We need the diamonds. No, I
don't think so.
So, all you have to do is press the
button in the middle, the brown button,
and then step back and enjoy the
machine. And then once it's complete,
Mumbo's mustache, wherever he is in the
universe, his mustache will be gone.
Good riddens.
Absolutely.
All right, here we go. Three, two, one,
and
Oh, the AFK song.
Oh, that's so good.
Mumbo mumbo AFK.
Yeah. Yeah.
Dash away.
There it goes.
That's so good. That is That's perfect.
Oh my god.
That's good.
I love the way he's like his mustache
comes off and it's like
Yeah. It's just like it's definitely
like one of those cartoons where it's
just like it's like when they have the
fake mustaches and it just kind of falls
off and he's like uh what's going on?
So now basically that's that's it for
now. What's happened is Mumbo's mustache
will have crawled off his face and gone
and scuttled away somewhere in the
Hermitcraft server. I don't know where.
You don't know where. Mumbo certainly
doesn't know where. And then it's either
up to Mumbo to find it or if he can't be
bothered, whoever finds it after after
that can return it if they want
or they could ransom it back to Mumbo.
I I'm thinking ransom.
Yeah, I know, right? I mean,
100%. Yeah.
I mean, how much is Mumbo willing to pay
to get his mustache back? Because we
can't activate this machine again until
he's got it back.
It's stuck like this until it's
returned.
There's only one Bumbo's mustache.
Now, I I live in America and it's
getting very cold because it's winter
time. I don't know if it's winter time
there or not, but that could be some
serious like face burn.
Oh, yeah. That's a face scarf right
there. That is a That is a lip warmer.
He's going to want that back.
Yeah, we definitely definitely need that
back. So,
so now that we've activated the machine,
it's actually been a little while. Mumbo
Jumbo is actually on the server. But
before we go and give him his share of
the money, I actually want to finish off
a bit of this base. We're going to be
doing a lot of work today, a lot of hard
grind. This base hasn't changed enough
in a long time. So, we're actually going
to work on the very top segment and
finally finish the main structure.
There's still not the details that I'd
like, but we're going to finish the main
bit. And then we're going to do
something very silly with the base. All
right, let's get into the time lapse.
So, we're going to be working on the
very last segment of this build, the
very top bit. It's going to look exactly
the same as the rest of the build, but
we still have time for a couple of
questions. It's only going to be a
minute long. Jake's World says, "Will
you ever post any other games other than
Minecraft?" The answer is yes, and
occasionally I do, but it has to be a
very special game or if it's a a
promotional video, then I may deviate
from the Minecraft, but for the most
part, it is going to stay Minecraft.
T707
says, "When is your house tour, please?"
Well, I'd love to show you guys around
in a house tour video on my second
channel. So, subscribe to that if you
would enjoy that. But I'm also scared
that people are going to find out where
I live. Gaming Bro 1 says, "Why is your
Twitter feed so filled with cats? And
how old are you?" Well, my Twitter feed
is filled with cats because my cats are
a huge part of my life. I absolutely
love them and I love taking pictures of
them. And I am 25. Are you going to
start uploading more building tutorials?
The answer is there's probably going to
be less building tutorials than there
were in previous years. The reason is
just there doesn't seem to be the same
demand from me on my channel for those
tutorials. They just don't perform as
well. And people have been asking more
about Hermitcraft and other series that
I do. So, until the demand for those
kind of videos comes back, I would
prefer to stay with the more
entertainment side of things as it is
slightly more enjoyable to make as well.
All right, that's all we have time for
today. Thank you very much for everyone
that gave me questions on Twitter. Let's
get back into it because Mumbo has just
come on the server. So, Mumbo is still
on the server here. So, what I'm going
to do is just deliver his half of the
profits. Now, I still don't know what to
do uh with this cuz this is a stack and
a half of diamond blocks. So, we need to
decide what to do, whether we're just
going to accept it cuz Jevin's
unbelievably rich. Let's go and be the
delivery boy for Mumbo's part of the
payment. Now, all we got to do is find
the stashless Matt. There he is. Now, in
theory, he should Ow. He He should not
have a mustache. Special delivery for
Rambo Jumbo. Yep. He's He's missing his
mustache.
Payment delivery.
Look at all that. making it rain. Hi,
Mumbo. So, I've just given you your half
of the payment, right?
Right.
That is what Je This is how it went
down. So, Jevvin left me that many
diamonds, three full stacks of blocks in
my base. So, I was a naughty. I went
back to the stash for cash shop and I
changed the book to say three stacks of
diamond blocks so that if he ever goes
back to check the price, that's what
it's going to say in the book.
That That is a tiny bit cheeky. It
is a bit cheeky, isn't it? Um I don't
actually plan on keeping these diamonds,
but I think we should see how long we
can carry this on for.
Yeah. Yeah. I I feel like I feel like
I mean I like it is nice having them.
Yeah, I know, right?
Like like I'm very tempted. I don't even
know what to do. I I I literally don't
know what to do with myself at this
point in time. Um,
I think it's safe to say we can spend
some of the diamonds because we actually
would have got a few stacks.
However,
I don't feel too good about actually
taking these diamonds, but and we will
make sure that Jeban gets them back in
the long run. But for now, while he has
no idea, we should totally play the the
game.
Yeah. Oh, for sure. And I mean, we could
try and invest them and then see if we
get more. No, that sounds like a that's
that's an easy way for us to lose all
the diamonds, isn't it?
Oh, yeah. We're definitely going to
lose. If we try and invest them, we're
definitely just going to lose them and
be like, "Jeffan, you you gave you
promised you gave us the money. Like,
what what do you want? You win some, you
lose some."
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Well, I guess we'll have to think
of something.
Yeah.
Something.
I think the key here is don't spend all
of them just in case he comes back and
gets mad. But
yeah,
at the same time, he doesn't even know.
Yeah. We can live the life for a bit.
Have fun. But also, let's take a look at
what this looks like finally.
My goodness, it actually looks complete.
It doesn't look like it's got anything
missing now. That is brilliant.
I really feel like my base is a
landmark. It is super impressive. I am
really enjoying this. Now, earlier I
mentioned I was going to do something
extremely silly.
And yeah, I am. And it's silly because I
don't have the resources to start this
project, but I'm going to do it anyway.
I'm going to build a giant ring all the
way around here. So, it's going to go
this wide. It's going to travel all the
way around. It's going to encompass the
little mail system. It's going to keep
going like this. this. I mean, it's
taking me a few seconds just to fly
around this circle at top speed. Think
how long this is going to take to make.
That took me ages. Just this little bit
down here took me who knows how long to
make a circle this big is absolutely
bonkers. So, I'm going to make like a
little walkway that goes all the way
around. And then you see where these
pillars are? I think I might try and
make pillars that go like the opposite
way but a little bit smaller. Hopefully
that makes sense in terms of a concept.
It should look excellent. It should look
really brilliant. I think the circle is
going to help build this area up
outwards because this build is so
insanely tall. It really needs a bit of
width. But all it needs is a little bit.
But a little bit at this scale, we're
talking thousands and thousands and
thousands of blocks. And I cannot afford
to get that circle wrong. Now, last
episode, some of you noticed that I had
a box up here called gem donations.
Okay, now if you open this up, someone
has this is actually Mumbo's gems that
he's kindly given to me. And a load of
people have also given me their gems.
Now, the gems aren't particularly used
on the server, but I the the beautiful
not quite poultry man. It wasn't me. It
was the man in the chicken costume is
going to do something with them. I'm
going to create a very fun game for all
of the hermits to enjoy. So, all I got
to do is head down here to the gem
collector, give him all my gems, turn
all of these into player heads. So, that
gave me a stack in a bit, and then I go
to this fella, and I scroll all the way
to my head, pop them in here, and I get
a bunch of green heads. Now, why am I
getting so many green heads? Well, this
is the fun bit. You see, I've been
collecting gems for a few weeks now, and
I have collected quite a substantial
amount of Grian heads, and that's
because I'm going to start the green
head hunt. So, this is going to be an
extraordinarily fun game where I hide
hundreds, and I mean hundreds, of my own
face around the server in places that
the hermits will never, never expect.
and we're going to start like an Easter
egg hunt but with my face. It's going to
be absolutely hilarious. So, the idea is
that I'm going to take all of these
physically and I'm going to place them
around the server. Some of them might be
easy, some of them might be a little
more hidden everywhere. Everywhere I can
think of. Okay, there's obviously a few
rules that have to be done with this.
So, number one, you cannot store your
green heads in a chest. This is a no no.
You can't store them like this, like
this, anywhere you like. You have to, if
you're going to play this game, you have
to store them like this. So, this might
mean that you're creating a Grian head
vault or some other method of storing
your Grian heads. But here's the real
fun part. Other hermits can steal your
Grian heads. So, you better protect your
Grian heads or someone is going to steal
my face from you. Their other rules are
fairly just, you know, gentleman's
rules. You cannot go and buy green heads
from the statue of Hermit. That is
definitely a no no. No green heads can
be purchased apart from myself if I want
to leave more in the game. And then
after a certain amount of time, the
person with the most green heads and I'm
going to have to go to people's bases
and count them. So if they Oh, there's
six green heads there. That's not very
good because there are stacks of them
around. And it should end up with a
pretty decent prize. And I'm going to
really grind hard to give a lot of
really, really good prizes. So, that's
pretty much the rules. What I'm going to
do is I'm going to make a green head
over in the shopping district, just a
small one. And if people want to
participate, all they got to do is read
the rules. And then once the competition
is done, I'm going to take down the
green head. Okay. We're going to make
something super temporary, not too
impressive, just so that we can get the
rules ac across. Just so that we can get
the rules across. What is this? Is this
the Oh my goodness. I think this is the
the Hermitcraft rail system. How awesome
is this? Uh-oh. Well, we're here in the
shopping district. Oh yeah, I forgot to
tell you. So, this is my little cart. As
everyone knows, we got a few bits of
profit here. I'm selling all of these
quartz as usual. ports is my way of
making diamonds on the server. And
basically what's been going on here is
exactly the same thing that's going on
with the log industry. So Zedaf, who
owns Quartz, Warts, and Shorts here, has
been buying my products, going straight
over to his shop and putting them in
here for a tidy tidy profit here. Not
cool.
So that's what he's been doing. So, he
is officially banned from my shop. I've
already raised the prices because he's
trying to undercut me. It's now two
diamonds for three stacks. But because
that's pretty funny, I've just banned
him from my shop. So, banned Hermits
Zaf.
So, if you catch him if you catch him
buying from my shop again, you let me
know and I'm going to confiscate all of
his stock again.
But we need to find a quick temporary
place to tell everyone about the green
head hunt. Perhaps here. Perhaps here is
a good place cuz it's right next to my
pickle shop and it's right next to the
rocket place and everyone uses the
rockets. Have I actually sold any
pickles recently?
No. No one wants pickles these days. So,
we're not going to do anything too fancy
at all. We're going to make a little
miniature green head right here. Nothing
too big.
I look so weird without a fringe. I
should always have my hair on. I'm a bit
like Mumbo. As soon as I take off my
hair, I look really strange. Look. So,
this is my fringe. It's kind of like my
whole thing. It's my identity. But if I
take it off, I look just as strange as
Mumbo. There we go. That's literally all
I'm going to do because again, after
this competition is over, that is it. It
is done. And I'm going to remove this
whole thing. So, I'm not going to waste
too much time making it all pretty and
nice because all this is is to grab
people's attention as a little notice
board. And I just need to do a few more
things, I think, to make this look a bit
more enticing. Right. I really hope I
haven't forgotten something here. Maybe
I should have done it in a book instead
of signs. But I might as well also start
actually placing them cuz that's going
to take the longest, I think, actually
placing these Grian heads everywhere.
Oh dear. So, it says, "Welcome to the
Grian Head Hunt. The head hunting game
that will win you prizes.
Grian heads have been placed all over
the server. All you have to do is
collect as many as you can. The hermit
with the most heads wins. Rules. You
must not store your heads in any chest.
Hopefully, that makes sense. You are not
allowed to buy more Grian heads. You can
steal other Grian heads if you find
them. And then it says, Grian will count
the hermit head supply on December the
1st. Good luck. So, I don't think I'm
going to tell them just how many heads
that I have because then they won't
know, you know, the total amount because
if they know that they've got over half,
they know they've won no matter what.
So, I think I'm going to keep that a
closely guarded secret and I'm probably
going to add even more green heads as I
go along. So, those are the rules. I
really hope I haven't missed anything.
There are absolutely no prizes in here
whatsoever yet, but I'm going to change
that immediately. And I think I'm going
to add more prizes as I go along. Scar,
scar, scar, your shop still has mobs
everywhere. Light this up. Look at Look,
a creeper's already blown this up. Oh my
goodness. So, what I've got here is the
prize that I think people will want the
most. This Grian will help you with any
prank. It's like an I owe you. So if
let's say that Jeban for example wants
to prank Mumbo and he won this, I would
be obliged to help him do it. Now I
won't do any prank for someone, but I
will help you finish your prank and even
make it a bit better if I can come up
with something. I need to make sure
straight away that I've got enough
prizes to entice people to participate
in this. So, I'm going to make sure that
I've got some of the best gifts you
could possibly get. And I already know
something that people really want, and
that is quartz. So, if I just take some
of the stock from here and pop it into
here, I can do two shulker boxes full of
quartz. Easy peasy. I am sacrificing
quite a lot of diamonds here, but this
should be really fun. This will be worth
it. Now, I'm going to be placing these
green heads absolutely everywhere. In
people's shops, in people's houses, in
people's mine shafts, everywhere.
It's going to take me a long time to do,
but it's going to be cool. I think this
is going to be really, really fun. Now,
that's as many as I'm going to place on
camera. The stacks and stacks of green
heads everywhere else. Well, I'm going
to hide those a little bit better. I'm
only showing you where I'm placing these
ones because I think these ones are
going to get found super easily anyway
and it doesn't really matter too much,
you know. So, I'm going to start hiding
them more carefully in places that you
definitely wouldn't even expect. It's a
real bummer giving away all of this
gravel because you've seen how much
white concrete I use in this in this
server. So, this is I'm giving away
something of real value here. I don't
want this competition to be worthless. I
think most of the stuff that I'm going
to give away as a prize are going to be
in the form of resources.
So, that's going to be enticing. Plus,
all of these shulker boxes. It's a
really good deal. Man, this looks really
rough with all of these heads here. I
maybe should have put this all in a book
because it doesn't look good. But, I
kind of like it as a billboard. It's
less less of a pain. So, this is the
prize chest. and more prizes will be
added over time. I'm going to start off
with this because I think this is
potentially a good place to start for
people that are interested in getting
some stuff. So, there's 64 diamonds.
Pretty standard. Grian will help you
with any prank. There is two Shulker
boxes full of gravel and there's two
Shulker boxes full of nether quartz.
Now, that is very valuable stuff right
there because you have to grind hard for
that kind of stuff. So, I think that's
probably where we're going to leave
today's episode with the advent of the
Grian Head hunt. So, there is two weeks
for everyone to find the green heads or
enough Korean heads to win the prize.
Okay, so thank you very much for
watching everyone and I hope everybody
has a really good time hunting these
green heads. Now, I am going to spend
many, many hours placing all of these
green heads. Now, obviously, I'm not
going to be participating cuz I
obviously know where they all are, but
this has been made exclusively just for
everybody to have a lot of fun with it.
So, thank you very much for watching
everyone. I'm going to get placing all
of these heads. And goodbye.
I hope no one tries to steal my head.
Like, my actual head. That would be bad.